(Penny:)Oh, Sheldon!
(Sheldon:)If it makes you
feel any better,
(Sheldon:)Thursday is no longer
Cruciferous Vegetable Night.
(Leonard:)Here's my chicken curry.
(Leonard:)Howard, your
shrimp biryani.
(Howard:)Thank you, sir.
Palak paneer,
that's Penny.
(Sheldon:)Thanks.
And for Rajesh
Koothrappali,
(Leonard:)from whose homeland
these tasty dishes originate,
(Leonard:)one large order of
chicken McNuggets.
(Penny:)Hey, what's my share?
Uh... 12 bucks.
(Penny:)Okay, can I get you after Friday
when I get paid?
Sure.
(Penny:)What am I up to now?
(Leonard:)Well, okay, with
the Indian food, the pizza,
(Leonard:)the Thai food, the tank of gas,
(Leonard:)the frozen yogurt
(Leonard:)and your rent, uh...
a little over $1,400.
(Penny(after Raj whispers to Howard and they both laugh):)What now?
(Howard:)He's just expressing
his admiration that
(Howard:)you don't even have to
put out to get free stuff.
(Penny:)It's not free-- I'm
gonna pay him back.